# **Ryan Fluharty**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ryan-fluharty

1920 S 3<sup>rd</sup> St Apt 71 · Waco, TX. 76706

(325) 201-2582 · R\_Fluharty@outlook.com

# **CAREER PROFILE**

Creative communicator with 7 years of experience in customer satisfaction. Trained in nonverbal, interpersonal, small group, and organizational communication styles. Also experienced with social media such as Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and LinkedIn, as well as social media software like Hootsuite. Looking to become an outstanding team member in the Public Relations and Communications field.

# **EDUCATION**

# **BAYLOR UNIVERSITY** –Waco, Texas **Bachelor of Arts**

May 2019

- Corporate Communication
- Training Project for Communication Training and Development Class

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **DCI Group**

June 2017 - August 2017

#### **PR Intern**

- Maintained detailed notes and transcriptions of events and hearings
- Ensured accurate mail and report labeling and data entry for Account Managers to report to clients on a daily basis
- Researched for the smallest details to give Account Managers the best chance to help the client
- Engaged with Instagram and Facebook users on behalf of the client as well as with Twitter users via Hootsuite
- Communicated effectively with Account Managers to help build workplace relationships in order to ensure the workplace experienced as few issues and mistakes as possible

# **Moody Library TechPoint**

#### **Shift Lead**

May 2018 - May 2019

- Innovated with Desk Coordinator to find new technologies to integrate to help the student body get the most out of their use of library services
- Acted as mediator with customer issues and as a lifeline to employees if any issue arose
- Led new hires with training on proper workplace behavior and procedures

#### **Study Commons Technician**

August 2016 - May 2018

- Developed working relationships with all employees to ensure a smooth workplace
- Ensured customer satisfaction with equipment rentals and technical issues
- Educated the student body about available technology and equipment available for use

#### ADDITIONAL SKILLS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Inducted to Lambda Pi Eta, the National Communication Association Honor Society (2016)
- Novice Spanish, both written and spoken
- Some experience with Adobe Photoshop
- Served as Band Council President (2018), Band Council Intramural Chair (2017), and Section Leader of the Tubas (2016-2018) in the Baylor University Golden Wave Band